I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
（竜介(りゅうすけ)）う…
"Fishing Hole"
Damn...
（竜介）チクショウ
"Live 19
'Blues'"
He's probably walking Beck.
（タマヨ）ベックの散歩
行ったんじゃないの？
For two days?
（サク）えっ ２日も？
He hasn't contacted you...
（コユキ）
連絡 ないんですよね？
（タマヨ）メイビー
Maybe...
（千葉(ちば)）ハァ…
（千葉）んんっ おい ばあちゃん！
心配じゃねえのかよ？
Hey, Grandma, aren't you worried?!
なあああ！
（コユキ・サク）いや…
No thanks...
Looks like Lucille's gone, too.
（コユキ）ルシールもないみたい
That guy...
（平(たいら)）あいつ… んっ！
（男性２）
京都に来たいなんて—
He wants to go to Kyoto...
Leon-san seems quite fond of Japan.
レオンさん 結構な
親日家なんですねえ
Yeah...I heard he was
influenced by his uncle.
（司会者）ああ 確か
叔父の影響だって—
聞いたことがあるけどな
Oh?
へえ～
彼は幼い頃から 叔父に
引き取られて 育てられたそうだよ
His uncle took him in when
he was little, and raised him.
叔父さんの嫁さんが
日本人だったそうだ
Seems his uncle's wife was Japanese.
レオンさんって いろいろあって
成功をつかんだ人なんすね
Leon-san has overcome much
in order to succeed, I guess.
（司会者）
詳しくは知らんが—
I don't know the details,
彼の体には アジア
アングロサクソン アフリカン…
but I hear he's got the blood
of five continents in his veins-
５つの大陸の血が
流れているそうだよ
including Asian, Anglo-Saxon and African.
５つですかあ
Five?
まっ あくまでも ウワサだがね
Of course, it's just a rumor.
何か… 怖いんですけど
-I find him a little scary.
-Yeah...
（ゴールディー：英語）
〈ボス！〉
Hi, Boss...
〈部屋には俺１人ですよ〉
Well, I'm here myself.
〈みんなは秋葉原(あきはばら)で
買い物じゃないっすか〉
I guess everyone is shopping
in Akihabara right now.
〈あの男？〉
That man?
〈大丈夫ですよ〉
That's fine.
〈ボコボコにしてやりましたから〉
I beat the hell outta him.
He won't even think
of running away from us.
〈もう逃げようなんて
思いませんよ〉
〈オーケー 10時に
東京(とうきょう)駅っすね〉
Okay, 10 o'clock. Tokyo Station?
〈ジャストに迎えに
行きますよ ボス〉
I'll pick you up on time, Boss.
（女の子）嫌～っ！
（竜介）んんっ!! ふんっ！
（ゴールディー）ああっ！
Fucking blood on my...I can't believe
this muthafucker hit me in the head!
I'll kill you, little fucker!
Damn it! You really pissed me off!
（ゴールディー）〈チクショウ！
マジでムカつくヤローだぜ！〉
（司会者：英語）
〈ミスターサイクス！〉
Mister Sykes...
〈ジョン・リー・デイビスという方を
御存知ですか？〉
Do you know the guy
called John Lee Davis?
〈会社に連絡がありました〉
He called you at the office.
He's in Japan right now as
a backup band for a soul singer.
〈彼は今 往年の
人気ソウルシンガーの—〉
〈バックバンドとして
来日中なんだそうです〉
Oh...I haven't seen him for three years...
（レオン：英語）
〈もう ３年も会ってないな〉
Oh?
（レオン）〈ジョン・リー・デイビスは
私の叔父だ〉
He, John Lee Davis, is my uncle.
（司会者）
〈たぶんテレビでも見てて—〉
He must have gotten to know Mr. Sykes'
coming to Japan, by TV or something.
〈ミスターサイクスの来日を
知ったんでしょう〉
（ゴールディー）
〈店の名前 クロスロードですか〉
Cross Road? That's classic...
〈ちょっとベタですね〉
〈その店に叔父さんが
いるんですか？〉
Is your uncle there at that restaurant?
〈叔父が来日すると
必ず行く店らしい〉
Yeah. He always goes there
when he visits Japan.
I see. Anyway Boss,
why do we wanna bring him?
（ゴールディー）
〈それにしても ボス〉
〈何で こいつまで
連れていくんです？〉
Punk ass never does anything, anywhere.
〈ルシールが見つかって—〉
I told him that we found the Lucille,
and that a Japanese musician stole it.
〈犯人が日本のミュージシャン
だったと話したら—〉
〈彼に会いたいと言われた〉
And now, he wants to see him.
（ゴールディー）〈面倒なことに
なりませんかね？〉
Isn't it going to be too much trouble?
〈犬はどうしてる？〉
How's that dog?
Hmph...He'll never take to me.
（ゴールディー）
〈全然 なつきませんね〉
（レオン）〈ブルース〉
The blues...
〈ロバート・ジョンソンか〉
Sounds like Robert Johnson...
（竜介：英語）〈意外だな〉
Surprising...
〈金の亡者
ＲＪレーベルの陰のボス—〉
Money mad boss, Leon Sykes,
talk about Robert Johnson?
〈レオン・サイクスの口から—〉
〈ロバート・ジョンソンの
名前が出るなんてな〉
（デイビス：英語）
〈おお レオンじゃないか！〉
Hey...Leon!
Come on...What are you putting
on that dreadful face for?
〈おいおい！〉
〈そんな怖い顔して
何考えてんだい？〉
I wouldn't sue you for money
like your dad did.
〈俺はお前のトーチャン
みたいに裁判起こして—〉
Come on, Leon. This is
your Uncle John Lee Davis!
〈お前さんから
金 巻き上げようなんて—〉
〈考えてねぇから心配すんな！〉
John...
〈ジョン〉
〈レオン〉
Leon...
（デイビス）
〈そいつが例の日本人かい？〉
Is that the Japanese?
（レオン）
〈ああ リュースケ・ミナミ〉
Yeah. Ryusuke Minami.
The fucked up punk
who used a picture of Lucille
〈シカゴのインディーズから—〉
〈ルシールをジャケットに使った
アルバムを出した—〉
for the album jacket that was released
by an Indies label in Chicago.
〈イカれた野郎さ〉
（ゴールディー）
〈何とか言え！〉
Say somethin'!
〈ちょっと手を洗ってきます〉
I'm gonna go wash my hands.
Yeah...
（竜介）〈さっきのプレイ
聞いて思ったんですけど〉
I was listening to you play, earlier.
Hey, brat...You still alive?
〈おう 小僧〉
〈生きてたか？〉
（竜介）〈もしかしたら—〉
You might be Mr. John Lee Davis?
〈あなたは ミスター
ジョン・リー・デイビスですか？〉
（デイビス）〈ほう！〉
Good...Now what about this?
〈じゃあ これは分かるかい？〉
〈1964年の
サンフランシスコでの演奏ですね〉
That's from the gigs
in San Francisco, 1964.
（レオン）〈おいおい〉
Hey...When were you born?
〈お前さん いったい
いつ生まれたんだい？〉
〈頼む 最後に
ミスターデイビスと—〉
Let me play with Mr. Davis, for my last...
〈セッションさせてほしい〉
〈お前さん そんな手で
弾けるのかい？〉
Can you play with hands like that?
Fortunately...my left hand is fine.
（竜介）〈幸運にも
左手は無事なんです〉
〈ほう！〉
Yeah...
〈ブルースってやつも
ナカナカいいっすねぇ〉
The blues...It ain't all that bad.
（レオン）〈しょせん
ビジネスには向かない音楽さ〉
Not good for business.
Sure ain't gonna make us rich.
（竜介）〈あなたのギターを
聞いていると—〉
Your guitar sound
reminds me of Sonny Boy.
〈なぜかサニーボーイを
思い出します〉
（デイビス）
〈そうかい？ ハハハハ！〉
Is that right?
〈サニーボーイは
俺の師匠だからな！〉
Sonny Boy is my master.
（竜介）〈マジですか！
じゃ ルシールは？〉
Jesus Christ! Then what about Lucille?
〈サニーボーイは
身寄りのない男でな〉
Sonny Boy had no one to depend on...
〈俺以外—〉
I was the only one who would
take Lucille on, after him.
〈ルシールを引き取ろうって
ヤツはいなかったのさ〉
But I don't have what
it takes to own Lucille.
〈でも ルシールは俺の器じゃ
デカ過ぎるシロモンよ〉
〈だから ルシールに
ふさわしい—〉
So if the real Blues Man for Lucille
showed up, I'd've handed it over to him.
〈本物のブルースマンが
出てきたら—〉
〈譲るつもりでいたんだよ〉
（竜介）〈あなたは
本物のブルースマンだ！〉
You are the real Blues Man.
（デイビス）〈実は一度
音楽を捨てたことがあってな〉
I gave up the music scene once...
〈ルシールは そんとき
レオンに預けたんだよ〉
I left Lucille to Leon, since then.
〈ミスター
ジョン・リー・デイビス〉
Mr. John Lee Davis, it was
a great honor to play with you.
〈あなたと弾けて光栄です
ありがとう〉
Thank you.
ドウイタシマシテ
Doitashimashite.
("You're welcome")
〈タバコ吸うか？〉
You want a cigarette?
No, thanks.
〈いらねーよ〉
（デイビス）
〈レオン あいつは本物だぞ〉
Leon, he is real.
〈今まで会った日本人で—〉
I've never seen any Japanese
who could express Blues that good.
〈彼ほどブルースを
理解している男はいなかった〉
And on top of that, he's really young.
〈そのうえ ヤツは
驚くほど若いじゃないか〉
〈エリカ・ブライジは
自殺じゃなく 殺されてて—〉
Erica Blige has been murdered,
and I heard rumor that you are the suspect.
〈しかも犯人は
お前だってウワサを聞いたよ〉
〈確かにエリカは
ＲＪレーベルを批判してたからな〉
Erica had been critical of the RJ label.
Leon...Would you kill
people for money, like this?
〈レオン〉
〈金のためなら
人殺しまでするのかい？〉
〈ヤツは殺すには惜しい男だぞ〉
He's too good to kill.
（レオン）〈叔父さん〉
Uncle...Even though you try to
live straight in this fucked up society...
〈こんなクソ社会じゃ
いくらまっとうに生きても—〉
〈しょせんは
しがない男で終わるだけだ〉
chances are, you'll die a loser.
〈それに どうせほとんどの人間が
しがなく死んでいくんだ〉
Most people die that way.
So I...
〈それなら俺は…〉
（竜介）〈クソみたいな音楽だな〉
What a fucking cheesy fucked up music!
（竜介）いて～っ！ ああっ！
Ouch!
（サク）竜介君が
いなくなってから もう４日だね
It's been four days since
Ryusuke-kun disappeared.
Yeah...
警察に届けたほうが
いいんじゃないかなあ…
Maybe we should report it to the police.
（サク）
もうすぐ ライブあるのにね
It's almost time for our performance.
はっ！ 釣り堀のおばあちゃんに
届け 出してもらおう！
-I'll have the lady at the
fishing hole make a report.
-Hey!
（千葉）お～い!!
（コユキ）ん？
（千葉）
コレコレ！ コレ！ うおおお！
-Take a look at this! Hey!
-Huh? Chiba-kun!
（コユキ）ああ！ 千葉君
（サク）
よいしょ どうかしたの？
Uh...Has something happened?
何だ おめえら まだ
知らねえんだなあ？
What...You two don't know about it?
フフフ… フ～ン
ジャーン!!
Ta-da!
"Maho Minami"
Ma...ho?
（千葉）フフ～ン
"Maho Minami-Sparkling 16-year-old"
Maho...Minami...
（コユキ）南… 真帆
Sixteen...
16歳…
（千葉）こりゃあ 真帆のヤツ
一気にブレイクするかもなあ～
"The moment the scent...
of excitement explodes."
She might well become
"The moment the scent...
of excitement explodes."
An overnight sensation.
"The moment the scent...
of excitement explodes."
全国で おめえらみたいに
かぶりついてるヤツが—
There are guys like you two all over
the nation, who'll be stuck on her.
大勢いるんだぜえ～！
（コユキ）べ 別に
かぶりついてるわけじゃないぞ！
I-I'm not stuck on her!
ヘヘヘへ～ それ やるよ
じゃあな～ ウハハハ…
You can have it. See you!
What are the two of you stuck on?
（益岡(ますおか)）２人して 何に
かぶりついてるんですか～？
（コユキ）あ いや ゲームの
攻略本… みたいな…
Uh, just a book that explains how to
conquer computer games...I guess...
Yeah, yeah...
Oh?
ふ～ん
（サク）コユキは真帆から
聞いてなかったの？
Didn't you hear about it
from Maho, Koyuki?
I haven't seen her lately.
She seems busy...
最近 全然 会ってないし
忙しそうだし…
Oh, Saku-chan, you have a nosebleed.
（益岡）あれ？
サクちゃん 鼻血 出てるよ
Ah!
Oh, Taira-kun! What's up?
お～う 平君かあ
うん どうしたの？
What?!
-What's the matter, Chiba-kun?!
-Yeah! I'll be right there!!
（コユキ）どうしたの 千葉君!?
（千葉）うん！ すぐ行く！
（コユキ・サク）どわあ！ 千葉君！
-Oh...Chiba-kun!
（千葉）おおい!! 竜介～!!
Hey! Ryusuke!
Yo...
よう
（平）あいつ ベックの
散歩に行ってたんだとさ
He says he was out walking Beck.
何で 包帯まみれなんだよっ！
Why are you all bandaged up?
竜介君 大丈夫？
Ryusuke-kun...Are you all right?
（サク）どこにいたの？
Where were you?
Where the heck are Beck and Lucille?!
おい！ ベックとルシールは
どうしたんだよ!?
（竜介）ハハッ まあさ
女とか金とか—
Well...Money and women...
Don't ask awkward questions, will you?
ヤボなこと 聞くなよな
W-W-Women?
おっ おっ 女…？
Money?
お金？
Anyway...Beck and Lucille
won't be coming back.
とにかく ベックとルシールは
もう戻らないんだ
（平）ちょっと 話してくる
（千葉）あとでな！
-I'll go and talk to him.
-See you later.
Yeah...
Really, man...What were you doing?
（千葉）ホントに おめえ
何してたんだよ！
-Shut up, will you?
-Come on...Be nice.
（竜介）うっせーなあ
（平）ほらほら 仲良くしろよ
Ryusuke-kun...
竜介君…
-It tastes a little different...
-Yeah...
Boy, our boss is really...
In other words...I wasn't worth killing.
（竜介）つまり俺は
殺す価値もない存在なんだ
〈そうさ 俺は金のためなら
人だって殺すだろう〉
Yeah...That's right. I do kill for money.
But I don't just murder people
for no reason.
〈でも 意味のない殺人は
しない主義だ〉
Now get the fuck outta here!
〈消えな コソ泥野郎！〉
こんな俺に 人の心を動かす
音楽なんて 作れんのかな
Can someone like me create music
that will move people?
（平）お前… 何 言ってんだ！
What are you saying?!
He's right! You're lucky to be alive!
（千葉）そうだよっ
生きて なんぼじゃん！
（コユキ）ねえ サク これ見て！
Hey, Saku! Look at this!!
"Pro-Am Welcome Auditions!!"
This would be a great chance!
これって すごいチャンスじゃん！
"Pro-Am Welcome Auditions!!"
Ohh...Auditions!?
（サク）
へえ！ オーディションかあ…
Ohh...Auditions!?
竜介君に教えてあげようよ
Let's tell Ryusuke-kun about it.
Good idea!
そうだね！
（コユキ）あっ！
I don't know about that...
（和緒(かずお)）
え～ それはどうかしら？
-Huh?
-Uh...
えっ？
（サク）あの～
（和緒）そのオーディションなら
２か月前に終わってるわ
Those auditions were over two months ago.
（コユキ）え？ そんな…
Huh? No way...
だいたい グレイトフルサウンドの
準備は １年かけてやるのよ
Besides, bands prepare a whole year
for that Grateful Sound event.
（サク）あっ あなたは…
A-And you are?
For your information,
the band that was chosen
ちなみに そのオーディションで
合格したバンドは—
ラ・マヒストル
was a promising newcomer called
"La Majistol" on the Ran label.
蘭(らん)のレーベルからの
期待の新人よ
Ran...
（コユキ）蘭…
-In other words...
The contest was rigged.
-Uh, ma'am...
つまり 出来レースってことね
（コユキ）あの オバさん—
-Ma'am?!
-This fishing hole is closed today.
オバ… さん？
んっ んんっ！
ここの釣り堀
きょうは定休日なんですけど
（和緒）ふん？
Huh?
Y-Y-Y-You...Are you the boy who sang
with Dying Breed in that Jim Walsh movie?
ボ ボ ボ ボ…
ボク もしかして—
ジム・ウォルシュの映画で
ダイブリと歌ってる少年!?
ええ そうですけど へヘッ
Yes. I am...
フッ これ～ あなたたちよね？
This...This is you guys, right?
Yes...
Mongolian Chop Squad is the
name of our band in America.
（サク）モンゴリアン・
チョップ・スクワッドは—
俺たちのアメリカでの
バンド名ですけど
（和緒）キャアアアッ！
やったわあああ!!
I did it! I finally found you!
I wasn't mistaken.
やっと やっと見つけたわ！
間違ってなかったんだ
My deductions were right,
after all! This is great!!
やっぱり 私の推理は
正しかったんだわ！
もうっ サイコー!!
Hey! Didn't I tell you
not to let customers in?!
（竜介）おい 客は
入れんなって 言っただろ！
（コユキ）あっ 客じゃないよ
っていうか 客だけど…
She's not a customer...
I guess she is...but not really...
いやっ そういう客ではなくて…
（サク）あの人 俺たちの
ＵＳ版のＣＤ 聞いて—
-That lady heard our American CD
and used it to find us.
-Eeek! I hooked something!
What should I do?!
それを頼りに 来てくれたんだ
-That lady?
-Somebody, help!
あの オバチャンが？
ふう～ん
Hm...Metal Glue...
“メタルグルー 佐藤 わ お”？
"Wao Sato-Metal Glue, Inc."
-Wa...o...Sato?
-Phew! It smells fishy...
"Wao Sato-Metal Glue, Inc."
-Here. Give it to me, please.
-Huh? Huh? What should I do?
（竜介）ハロー？
-Hello?
-Hey, Ray...What the fuck're you doing?
（真帆：英語）
〈おい 竜介 何してたんだよ！〉
Oh! I'm sorry, I'm kinda busy...
Just a sec...
（竜介）〈あぁ ワリィ
今 忙しいってゆうか〉
（竜介）おい！ コユキ
Hey! Koyuki...
Huh? What is it?
（コユキ）あっ 何？
Hello?
Koyuki?
（真帆）コユキ？
Ryusuke-kun's back safely.
（コユキ）
竜介君 無事に戻ったよ！
He was probably over at some girl's.
どうせ 女のとこにでも
いたんでしょ～？
あっ それよりさあ きょう
先行ロードショーなんだぞ
Never mind that...
There's a sneak preview of the
Dying Breed tour movie today!
ダイブリのツアームービー
What?! The Dying Breed movie?!
（コユキ）ええっ!?
ダイブリの映画？ もしもし？
Hello?
Koyuki, you want to see it with me?
（真帆）
ね コユキ 一緒に見ない？
（コユキ）うん！
（サク・千葉）へヘッ
-Yeah!
-Mm...
（コユキ）俺 ちょっと…
-I gotta go...
-Yes! Go on!!
おーし！ 行ってこい！
（コユキ）サク？
（サク）へヘッ！
Saku...
（コユキ）
それじゃあ これ 竜介君に！
Okay! Give this to Ryusuke-kun, will you?!
（平）いいねえ 青春しててさ
How nice...
He's enjoying his youth.
（真帆）遅いぞ～
You're late!
ハァ ハァ…
I just got a call from Yoshito.
ちょうど ヨシトから
電話があってさあ—
He said he wanted to
see the movie too, so...
ヨシトも映画 見たいって言うから
（ヨシト）男と２人っていう
シチュエーションは—
Being with two guys...
isn't very good for Maho's future.
真帆の将来のためにも
よくないしね
アッハッハ アハハ
ヨシト君 プログラム 見る？
Yoshito-kun, you want
to look at the program?
俺 映画の前に
読まない主義～
I never read it before a movie.
Oh...
On the stage, they are perfect.
They're flawless.
Yes they are...And maybe not,
depending on your point of view.
Ahem. Excuse me...
Everybody has a life, a daily life.
There's no exception; they do.
Conflict with their agent?
It's none of our business!
Of course, Eddy. These guys
are the next big thing in Japan.
If we like them at the rehearsal,
yeah, we could play with them.
Belle Ame...It means
"beautiful spirit" in French.
Bugger off. Hit the road.
-Jim, give me that!
-After all, Eddy is just a guy.
-Hey! They're waiting for us.
-Why are you saying this now? Shit!
-But, that makes Dying Breed appealing.
-What shall we do? That's irresponsible.
Hey Jim! What are you filming!?
-On top of that, Matt is wild.
Like a river flowing,
inspiration always flows from my mind.
-Hey! Dancing, dancing...Party man...
-Oh! He's a funny guy.
-Happy birthday to you...
（一同）
ハッピーバースデー トゥー ユー
（男性）エディ！
Sometimes, there comes a special day,
while they're on tour.
It's a beautiful scene.
Tokyo...a city of noise
and chaos. Techno-city.
Come on!
They had a live here, as well.
In the evening, with the shining moon...
They met a boy. It was
a very special event.
（コユキ）何か すごいことが
起こりそうな—
I felt like something great...
予感がしたんだ
...was about to happen.
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
（千葉）佐藤のオバチャンって
おもしれえよな！
That Sato lady was funny, wasn't she?
"Live 20
'Grateful Sound'”
Next episode: Grateful Sound!
Will Beck be able to perform?
次週…
ＢＥＣＫは
出場できるのかな？